investorlinks.com 2000-12-06

# InvestorLinks Privacy Statement

|    

> **On Nov. 17th, 2000, INVESTORLINKS version 2.0 was launched.
> 
> You have reached a page on InvestorLinks that has been changed. The below link will take you to the new site. 
> 
> To go to the new INVESTORLINKS:   [CLICK HERE](http://www.investorlinks.com/index.html).
> 
> **

Privacy Statement    

InvestorLinks.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 
* **Special note to our users:** _This site uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to[http://www.engage.com/privacy](http://www.engage.com/privacy/)._ **1\. Information InvestorLinks.com gathers and tracks**

InvestorLinks.com uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. InvestorLinks.com gathers two types of information about users: data that users provide through optional, voluntary registration on several of our sites, such as requesting subscription to our newsletter, filling out our user's survey form, and through optional, voluntary participation in certain contests (when they are run); and aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. 

Because InvestorLinks.com derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. The only situation in which InvestorLinks.com divulges information about an individual user to a third party is with certain contests, and then, only with the user's express consent. 

Our site's offer a daily emailed financial newsletter. Subscription requires users to give us their email address only. Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter. 

Email addresses sent to InvestorLinks are kept on a separate server, and are never used for any purpose other than what the person sending them requested. They are not sold or shared with any other website, list, or service for any reason. 

**2\. InvestorLinks.com - Links to Other Websites**

This site contains links to other sites. InvestorLinks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**3\. InvestorLinks.com - Surveys**

Occasionally InvestorLinks.com conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for financial information (like their houshold income and overall size of their investment portfolio) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

**4\. InvestorLinks.com - Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**5\. InvestorLinks.com - Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

InvestorLinks.com does not use cookies. 

**6\. InvestorLinks.com - Use of the information**

InvestorLinks.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

As stated above, InvestorLinks.com uses information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls and message boards. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. InvestorLinks.com never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers or partners. 

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. InvestorLinks.com does not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

InvestorLinks.com creates aggregrate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because InvestorLinks.com doesn't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. 

**7\. InvestorLinks.com - Sharing of the information**

InvestorLinks.com uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We do not share information about individual users with any third party, except in the case of some contests, and then, only with a user's express consent. 

InvestorLinks.com does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly. 

**8\. InvestorLinks.com - Delete/deactivate policy**

Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter. 

**9\. InvestorLinks.com - Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

InvestorLinks.com  
IL Data Corporation, Inc.  
2350 Saddle Hollow Rd, Suite 1  
Crozet, VA 22932  
mailto:info@investorlinks.com  
(877) 823 8182 Toll Free   
(804) 823-8182 Local   
(804) 823-8183 Fax
